

# TALIANA CHUMACHENKO

Test Automation Engineer

#### 0973269709

#### taliana.slava@gmail.com

Lviv

### **EDUCATION**

National Forestry University of Ukraine 2019-2022

Techical college of Lviv polytechnic 2015-2019

## **SKILLS**

C#/Basic Python HTML/CSS/Xpath XML/ JSON

MySQL

Git/Jira/TFS

WEB/API

NUnit/TestNG/Selenium

Page Objects/Selenium/WebDriver

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a C# Automation QA Engineer with three years of experience at SoftServe. I have primarily worked with Web testing and have experience with API testing. Additionally, I have taken lessons on using the Postman tool to keep my knowledge updated. Also took a basic course on Python. I am a fast learner and am always willing to acquire new knowledge and take on challenges.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

O Jul 2020 - Apr 2024 SoftServe, Lviv

### Test Automation Engineer

The petroleum industry also known as the oil 8 gas industry, includes the global processes of exploration, extraction, refining, transporting and marketing of petroleum products

- Software testing
- Participated in the development of automated tests and test
- framework
- Writing test documentation: Bug reports, Test Cases
- Wrinting documentation
- Mentorship

Feb 2020-Jun 2020 SoftServe, Lviv

# Test Automation Engineer

A software solution for sales representatives. Allows sales to communicate with the end clients efficiently, provides different combination of services and their cost at once, ability to sign the contract on the spot.

- Analyzing user stories and requirements:
- Software testing
- Participated in the development of automated tests and test
- framework (Web, API)
- Writing test documentation: Bug reports, Test Cases

### LANGUAGE

English

Ukranian

## **COURSES**

SoftServe IT Academy

2019-2020